export default [
    {
        question: 'Which command extracts data from a database?',
        options: ['SELECT', 'UPDATE', 'DELETE', 'INSERT INTO', 'CREATE DATABASE'],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Which command updates data in a database?',
        options: ['ALTER DATABASE', 'CREATE TABLE', 'ALTER TABLE', 'CREATE DATABASE', 'UPDATE'],
        correct: 4
    },    
    {
        question: 'Which command deletes data from a database?',
        options: ['DROP TABLE', 'DELETE', 'ALTER DATABASE', 'DROP INDEX', 'ALTER TABLE'],
        correct: 1
    },    
    {
        question: 'Which command inserts new data into a database?',
        options: ['CREATE TABLE', 'CREATE INDEX', 'INSERT INTO', 'CREATE DATABASE', 'SELECT'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which command creates a new database?',
        options: ['ALTER TABLE', 'ALTER DATABASE', 'CREATE TABLE', 'CREATE INDEX', 'CREATE DATABASE'],
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'Which command modifies a database?',
        options: ['UPDATE', 'INSERT INTO', 'ALTER DATABASE', 'CREATE INDEX', 'ALTER TABLE'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which command creates a new table?',
        options: ['CREATE DATABASE', 'CREATE INDEX', 'ALTER TABLE', 'CREATE TABLE', 'DROP TABLE'],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Which command modifies a table?',
        options: ['UPDATE', 'INSERT INTO', 'SELECT', 'ALTER DATABASE', 'ALTER TABLE'],
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'Which command deletes a table?',
        options: ['DROP INDEX', 'DELETE', 'DROP TABLE', 'ALTER TABLE', 'ALTER DATABASE'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which command deletes an index?',
        options: ['ALTER TABLE', 'ALTER DATABASE', 'DELETE', 'CREATE INDEX', 'DROP INDEX'],
        correct: 4
    }
]